🛮 +1 (765) 701-5596 | 🗷 sgchi@purdue.edu | 🏕 https://jisk984.github.io | 🖸 jisk984 | 🛅 seunggeun-chi-963050153 | 📂 Seunggeun Chi

# **Research Interests**

My research interests lie in **Machine Learning** and its applications to real-world problems. **Representation Learning** in **Computer Vision** problems is my primary study. My research also spans over **Combinatorial Optimization** problems which aim to extract rules by applying **Reinforcement Learning**.

## **Education**

Purdue University West Lafayette, U.S.

Ph.D. STUDENT IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Aug. 2021 - current

• C-Design Lab, Advisor: Karthik Ramani

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

M.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Mar. 2019 - Aug. 2021

• Optimization Lab, Advisor : ByungRo Moon

Seoul National University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

• Computer Architecture Lab, Advisor: SangLyul Min

**Publications** 

**Conference Proceedings** 

• M. H. Ha, **S. Chi**, S. Lee. Learning to Escape to Promised Lands: Multi-mode Policy Learning for the Traveling Salesmen Problem. *IEEE Transactions on Neural Networks and Learning Systems (TNNLS)*, 2022, submitted

• [C2] H, Chi, M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition. IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2022

• [C1] M. H. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Y. Cha, B. R. Moon. Evolution-based Meta Reinforcement Learning for Portfolio Optimization. In proceedings of the 23rd *The Genetic and Evolutionary Computation Conference (GECCO), 2021* 

Research & Project

#### HandVAE: An interactive 3D hand generation system

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Sept. 2021 - Apr. 2022

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Targeting UIST 2022

· Disentangled properties of hands with Beta-VAE

• Developed UI for interactive hand generation and annotation

• Developed federated learning system

#### **Learning Joint Relations for Predicting Pose under Occlusion**

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

Sept. 2021 - Mar. 2022

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Targeting ECCV 2022
Applied the self-supervised learning to make the model understand joint relations and infer occluded joint from visible joints

State-of-the-art performances on 3D Hand Pose Estimation datasets

#### **Weakly Supervised Action Segmentation for Video**

C-Design Lab, Purdue Univ.

July. 2020 - Sept. 2020

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

• Introduced a loss function for video segmentation combining Triplet loss and Temporal Cycle Consistency Loss

- Defined the Action Segmentation problem as a Neural Machine Translation problem
- Visualized the attention matrices to interpret Machine's inference

# Improving Multi-Joint dynamics with Contact(MuJoCo) by applying Hierarchical Reinforcement Learning

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

• Proposed a hierarchical architecture to give the agent frequent reward signals by setting subgoals

- Designed and developed a hierarchical architecture of model and environment
- Applied policy gradient with self-critical sequence training in optimization

Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2020

SEUNGGEUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE

#### Predicting stock price by applying Combinatorial Optimization

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

OptLab, Seoul National Univ.

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

ArchiLab, Seoul National Univ.

Jan. 2019 - Jun. 2019

Aug. 2018 - Jan. 2019

Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

- · Analyzed data with the ANOVA(Analysis of variance) method and Regression method
- · Applied Genetic Algorithm, Evolutional Computation, and Fourier transformation to find better solutions
- Applied distributed computing to accelerate independent computation

#### Accelerating computation of Machine Learning by using Field-Programmable Gate Array

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- · Applied methods of SIMD(Single Instruction Multiple Data) with the low-level language of Verilog
- Reduced data size with SVD(Singular Value Decomposition)
- Rearranged units to utilize parallel computation

#### Designing spatial-navigation on chrome-extension

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

- · formulated malfunctioning cases and defined user-friendly environment
- Developed user-friendly navigation UI
- https://github.com/WICG/spatial-navigation

# Skills

#### **Research and Development Stacks**

**Major Languages** Python, C/C++, java, Verilog Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow **Computer Vision** OpenCV, OpenGL

Web Languages Nginx, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Database MySQL, SQLite

# Other Tools and Skills

**Other Langauges** Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab, R **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

**Text Editors & IDE** Vim, VSCode, Eclipse Software SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

VCS Git

# Working Experience \_

**SK Hynix** Icheon, S.Korea

INTERN RESEARCHER Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- · Designed an exclusive chip for testing 3D NAND flash architecture and verified the reliabilty of existing architectures
- Developed a module for predicting locality of data and tested it with real data

#### **Korean National Police Agency**

**DOKDO SECURITY POLICE** 

· Defended the disputed territory as a squad leader

#### Dokdo, S.Korea

Dec. 2013 - Sep. 2015

# **Teaching Experience**

CS.4190.681A	Genetic Algorithm, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.407	Algorithm, 2019-fall, 2020-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.M1522.407	Data Structure, 2019-spring, 2020-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.4190.308	Computer architecture, 2018-spring	Teaching Assistant
CS.035.001	<b>Digital Computer Concept and Practice</b> , 2017-fall, 2018-fall	Teaching Assistant
PE.051.004	Volley ball, 2018-fall, 2019-spring, 2021-spring	Teaching Assistant

## Honors & Awards

1ST PLACE

### Competition of accelerating General-Purpose GPU sponsored by Intel

Korea Ministry of Science and ICT

Manycore Programming Lab

## The National Scholarship for Science and Engineering

FULL SCHOLARSHIP Mar. 2018 - Aug. 2021

SEUNGGEUN CHI · CURRICULUM VITAE